Oh man, we'll just go right to
questions.
>> All right.
All right. Here we go. Who's got it
first? A lot of people comparing
D'Angelo to you. What do you think when
you you hear that?
>> Uh D'Angelo is his own man and he's a
he's a guy again that we love. Um man,
the trait speak for himself. I mean,
when it comes to height, weight, and all
that, but then again, you look at the um
the physical uh characteristics of the
player, and that just overcomes a lot of
the the the traits that he have as far
as his height and all that. So, love the
player, tough, aggressive, come from a
winning program. Um that's been
something that's been constant about
what we've been doing. Um he's a damn
good player.
>> Is he going to be a slot guy for you?
>> Well, he's going to play slot. He's
going to play on the outside. So, we
made a cross train in that aspect. He
did it in college. So, um that's nothing
new to him.
>> Would you say it's better to describe
him as shorter but not small because he
seems to be thickly built and he plays
the run very well?
>> Well, he is a tough guy. Um the thing is
he just like you can't judge the heart.
That's one thing that when you start to
talk to guys, you start to see guys
play, you start to understand what the
heart is about. So, um listen, I know
he's a shorter corner, but again, his
play speaks for itself.
from a a scouting perspective. What you
have to see to make an exception to
maybe a high rle quarterback or you know
>> Yeah, it's a good question. You got to
see him do it and that's the thing. He's
done it. He's been very productive and
been productive at a high level against
good competition. And it's funny, we we
ask wide receivers that we interview,
whether it's combine, all-star games,
guys we bring in for visits, we often
ask them like, "Who's the best corner
you're going to go against?"
numerous guys if they f if they've faced
pawns all of them pawns um he's he's
just been a productive football player
despite the size limitations he finds a
ways to get stops he covers guys he's
one of the better tacklers in this draft
regardless of position um so excited to
have him good football player winning
program
>> you guys have talked about bringing in
winners a lot the last last couple of
days have there been players that maybe
had the had the skills that you were
looking for but not that element that
that you passed on or or dropped them
down your boards?
>> No, I wouldn't say that we dropped
anyone because they came from a losing
program or anything like that, but we
have discussions. I mean, we cover
everything when we talk about these
prospects. Um, and when they're coming
from winning programs, it it means
something.
>> How hard did you try to get back into
the third round?
>> Yeah, there was a lot of action all day
today, you know, moving up, moving back.
Um we we called on a few there at the
end, but it just didn't materialize, but
we feel good about where the board's at
going in tomorrow with the with the
three picks in the fourth round and the
two and the seven. So, we're excited.
>> Do you um anticipate taking a
quarterback at some point tomorrow?
>> I don't The board's wide open. Just
again sticking to the theme of taking
good players that can help the team. I
wouldn't commit to any one position. Did
you move out of uh 44 because somebody
came off the board right before there?
>> No, we felt good with where the board
was at at 44 with a good group of
players, six to seven players that we
really liked. So that 50 mark was good
and we had our eye on on on ponds and
and had a good feel that he could uh
potentially still be still be there and
and he wasn't. It worked out. When you
talk about winning programs, guys come
from like what do you notice that's
different about them when you're when
you're around them? When you're watching
the film and things like that, what do
you see that's different?
>> Well, we know they come from a culture
where they've felt winning before.
They've seen it typically to a standard
on how they operate. Um
>> yeah, usually when you come from a
winning program um like you really know
how it looks and when you join another
program um you bring that same mentality
um to that program to help that program
elevate where it is. And anytime you can
you can do that with a number of
players, it just only elevates your
team. And they're going to practice,
they're going to go through meetings,
they're going to go through walkthrough
like winners do and that permeates
throughout your whole team. So, um, and
Moo said it before, man. Listen, we
didn't discredit guys from a losing
program at all. You know, we were just
getting the best players that we can
get. It just so happen these guys have
come from winning program, which is a
plus for us.
>> Is there something AG about the Indiana
things a little different when you say
programs,
>> it's not Ohio State, it's not Alabama.
This is a program that became a winner
in the last two years, right? Like, and
these guys were part of that. like do
they do they have another intangible of
kind of you know turning something
around?
>> Well, when you look at um I guess Pawns
for example, so he came from I think
with JMU you know with um you know with
the same winning program with the coach
>> um and it it's man it's one of those
things to where it was an amazing run
you know to watch those guys and see how
they operated. But on another note, he
is another guy that made like huge plays
in critical situation at critical times
um to help that team win. And that's
another trait that you know that we
looked at on all these guys. Who are the
pressure players? Who are the players
that can make consistent plays when the
pressure's on and he did that on a
number of occasions. So, um again, we
can go through and talk about the
height. We can go through and talk about
the weight, but man, when you just watch
the the the the player play, I mean,
just look at all the plays that he made
and look at all the um the tackles that
he made. Um he always he always helped
the team put us put itself in a position
to win and that's a trait that you want
to bring on your team.
>> How do you see your quarterback
position? You added a couple of guys
like Hans and Wright in the offseason.
How do you see the whole thing shaking
out now? Well, it's it's going to be a
competition and and the guys know that
and anytime you can create competition
within your team, it only makes your
team better. Um, especially in practice
because now that that transitions to
game play when you can have that type of
competition on a daily basis, man, you
start to see the game actually tick up a
little bit as far as how we play.
>> Did you guys kind of have a theme of
production over potential? It seems like
the four guys you picked in the first
two rounds produced week in and week
out. It wasn't like you're rolling the
dice on a size speed guy who was maybe
inconsistent.
>> Yeah, like I've mentioned before, we
talk about both all the time, the
production and potential. And it's nice
when when they have both and there's
still growth potential for these
players, which many of them have, but
it's important that these guys are
productive and a lot of them have been
productive.
All
>> good. See you tomorrow.
>> Thanks, guys. Thanks.